<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.5.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2017-10-14T00:18:41-04:00</updated><id>/</id><title type="html">Brassfield Road Elementary School PTA</title><entry><title type="html">Character Parade - Tuesday, 10/31</title><link href="/events/2017/10/31/character-parade.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Character Parade - Tuesday, 10/31" /><published>2017-10-31T13:45:00-04:00</published><updated>2017-10-31T13:45:00-04:00</updated><id>/events/2017/10/31/character-parade</id><content type="html" xml:base="/events/2017/10/31/character-parade.html">&lt;p&gt;Calling all characters! Book characters, that is! In a celebration of reading, Brassfield students will parade the school on October 31st carrying their favorite book, dressed as their favorite character. Classrooms across the school will tie the experience to grade level curriculum. From Winnie the Pooh to Harry Potter we can't wait to bring books to life! Be on the lookout for specific information on how to participate from your teacher. Track 3 families are encouraged to come back to school and participate, but be sure to check into the front office with Kimberly when you arrive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;signed&quot;&gt;Registered Volunteers - &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.signupgenius.com/go/5080b4ea9af2eabf58-school&quot;&gt;Sign up to assist&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Calling all characters! Book characters, that is! In a celebration of reading, Brassfield students will parade the school on October 31st carrying their favorite book, dressed as their favorite character. Classrooms across the school will tie the experience to grade level curriculum. From Winnie the Pooh to Harry Potter we can't wait to bring books to life! Be on the lookout for specific information on how to participate from your teacher. Track 3 families are encouraged to come back to school and participate, but be sure to check into the front office with Kimberly when you arrive. Registered Volunteers - Sign up to assist</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Artopia after Early Release! Friday, 10/20</title><link href="/events/2017/10/20/artopia.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Artopia after Early Release! Friday, 10/20" /><published>2017-10-20T13:45:00-04:00</published><updated>2017-10-20T13:45:00-04:00</updated><id>/events/2017/10/20/artopia</id><content type="html" xml:base="/events/2017/10/20/artopia.html">&lt;p&gt;Join us at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.artopia-raleigh.com/book-online&quot;&gt;ARTOPIA&lt;/a&gt; on Oct. 20th for early release! We will have 2 sessions available one from 1:45 - 2:45 and the second from 3:00 - 4:00, as well as the  option to add on an Artarama hour.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions please contact &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:katiescott22@gmail.com&quot;&gt;Katie Scott&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The $12 session will include a variety of fall crafts! The artarama hour is a 1hour canvas painting session and is open to children 3+ and adults.  Please use the link below to register online, scroll down until you see the Brassfield Fundraiser, you can add on the Artarama hour at checkout!  Don’t forget 50% comes back to Brassfield!</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Join us at ARTOPIA on Oct. 20th for early release! We will have 2 sessions available one from 1:45 - 2:45 and the second from 3:00 - 4:00, as well as the option to add on an Artarama hour. If you have any questions please contact Katie Scott</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">K-3 Mandate Presentation and Discussion - PLEASE REGISTER</title><link href="/events/2017/10/16/k-3-mandate-presentation.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="K-3 Mandate Presentation and Discussion - PLEASE REGISTER" /><published>2017-10-16T19:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2017-10-16T19:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/events/2017/10/16/k-3-mandate-presentation</id><content type="html" xml:base="/events/2017/10/16/k-3-mandate-presentation.html">&lt;p&gt;
What: Advocacy Presentation and Discussion&lt;br&gt;
Who will be presenting: Wake County PTA Council and Public Schools First NC&lt;br&gt;
When:&lt;b&gt;Monday, 10/16&lt;/b&gt;, from 7-8pm&lt;br&gt;
Where: Brassfield Road Elementary School Media Center&lt;br&gt;
For:  Brassfield, Baileywick, and Wakefield ES parents and area PTA Boards.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;signed&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.SignUpGenius.com/go/5080B4EA9AF2EABF58-advocacy&quot;&gt;Please RSVP to attend here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The North Carolina Legislature passed an unfunded K-3 class size mandate
last spring which will take full effect in 2018-2019.  Join us on October
16 to hear about the mandate, how it will affect Wake County Public
Schools, and the possible solutions offered by the school district to deal
with the new requirements.  We will also discuss what PTA units, leaders,
members and parents can do to advocate for our students and teachers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Come join us to be part of an open discussion of strategy ideas to affect
change! Questions? &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:school@gopack.org&quot;&gt;Tania&lt;/a&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">What: Advocacy Presentation and Discussion Who will be presenting: Wake County PTA Council and Public Schools First NC When:Monday, 10/16, from 7-8pm Where: Brassfield Road Elementary School Media Center For: Brassfield, Baileywick, and Wakefield ES parents and area PTA Boards. Please RSVP to attend here.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Book Fair Volunteer Information Session - Monday, 10/16</title><link href="/events/2017/10/16/book-fair.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Book Fair Volunteer Information Session - Monday, 10/16" /><published>2017-10-16T14:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2017-10-16T14:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/events/2017/10/16/book-fair</id><content type="html" xml:base="/events/2017/10/16/book-fair.html">&lt;p&gt;The book fair committee is looking for volunteers to help with our Winter Book Fair!  We will have an informational meeting at 2:00pm on Monday, October 16th in the Learning Commons to go over areas where help is needed and the estimated time commitment for each job.  Some items can even be done from home, and no amount of help is too small! This year, all proceeds from the fair will go towards improving our library collection, so please stop in and see how you can help make this fundraiser a success! Questions? &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:Ericatadd@Hotmail.com&quot;&gt;Email Erica Tadd&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;signed&quot;&gt;-Thanks,The Book Fair Committee&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">The book fair committee is looking for volunteers to help with our Winter Book Fair! We will have an informational meeting at 2:00pm on Monday, October 16th in the Learning Commons to go over areas where help is needed and the estimated time commitment for each job. Some items can even be done from home, and no amount of help is too small! This year, all proceeds from the fair will go towards improving our library collection, so please stop in and see how you can help make this fundraiser a success! Questions? Email Erica Tadd -Thanks,The Book Fair Committee</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Movie Night at Brassfield - Friday, 10/13</title><link href="/past_events/2017/10/13/movie-night.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Movie Night at Brassfield - Friday, 10/13" /><published>2017-10-13T18:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2017-10-13T18:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/past_events/2017/10/13/movie-night</id><content type="html" xml:base="/past_events/2017/10/13/movie-night.html">&lt;p&gt;Friday, October 13th at 6:00pm&lt;br&gt;
MOVIE: The movie &lt;b&gt;&quot;Trolls&quot;&lt;/b&gt; will start in the Multi-Purpose room at 6:30pm &lt;br&gt; 
KIDS - COME IN COSTUME!!    COME DRESSED AS YOUR FAVORITE CHARACTER (MOVIE, BOOK, ETC.) !&lt;br&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;signed&quot;&gt;Registered Volunteers - &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.signupgenius.com/go/5080b4ea9af2eabf58-school&quot;&gt;Sign up to assist&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
PIZZA:  Pizza and drinks will be served at 6pm in the cafeteria.      Cheese and pepperoni pizza will be available by the slice for $1.00/slice and assorted drinks will be available for $1.00/each. &lt;br&gt; 
Bringing the family for dinner?  You can order a whole pizza for just $10.00!  Whole pizzas will be available through pre-order only.  Please email Melinda Hemphill at jaymelinda@yahoo.com on or before October 11th and let us know if you’d like cheese or pepperoni (or half&amp;half).&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
CANDY:  Assorted boxed candy/snacks will also be available in the cafeteria for $1.00/box.&lt;br&gt;
Please remember that children are not to be left in the multi-purpose room unattended.  We respectfully ask that you supervise your children at all times.
&lt;br&gt;
You are welcome to bring blankets, pillows, chairs, etc!&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Friday, October 13th at 6:00pm MOVIE: The movie &quot;Trolls&quot; will start in the Multi-Purpose room at 6:30pm KIDS - COME IN COSTUME!! COME DRESSED AS YOUR FAVORITE CHARACTER (MOVIE, BOOK, ETC.) ! Registered Volunteers - Sign up to assist</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">NC State Fair Tickets</title><link href="/past_events/2017/10/12/nc-state-fair.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="NC State Fair Tickets" /><published>2017-10-12T14:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2017-10-12T14:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/past_events/2017/10/12/nc-state-fair</id><content type="html" xml:base="/past_events/2017/10/12/nc-state-fair.html">&lt;p&gt;Support Brassfield by purchasing tickets in advance of the N.C. State Fair! The State Fair will donate $2 to Brassfield for every adult ticket purchased and $1 for every child ticket purchased.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Simply enter the code 334 under &quot;Membership&quot; at check-out on the WCPSS Admission Ticket link. Tickets must be purchased by 11:59 p.m. on Thursday, Oct. 12.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Support Brassfield by purchasing tickets in advance of the N.C. State Fair! The State Fair will donate $2 to Brassfield for every adult ticket purchased and $1 for every child ticket purchased. Simply enter the code 334 under &quot;Membership&quot; at check-out on the WCPSS Admission Ticket link. Tickets must be purchased by 11:59 p.m. on Thursday, Oct. 12.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Greetings from Wake County PTA</title><link href="/2017/09/26/hello-from-wake-county-pta.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Greetings from Wake County PTA" /><published>2017-09-26T16:42:51-04:00</published><updated>2017-09-26T16:42:51-04:00</updated><id>/2017/09/26/hello-from-wake-county-pta</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2017/09/26/hello-from-wake-county-pta.html">&lt;p&gt;Hello everyone,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you for your engagement on this issue!  I look forward to working with all of you as we advocate for our schools, teachers and students regarding this class size mandate. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I created the attached flier that you are welcome to use at your schools to educate parents and families about this issue and its effects on WCPSS schools.  This flier has been reviewed by staff with the school district to make sure my bullet points are correct.  Please distribute widely and get your families engaged and informed on this &quot;class size chaos.&quot;  The more people we have talking about it and contacting state legislators, the better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; If you haven't joined our Advocacy hub on &lt;a href=&quot;https://wakepta.memberhub.com/hub/WakePT96219 &quot; onclick=&quot;trackOutboundLink('https://wakepta.memberhub.com/hub/WakePT96219 ')&quot;&gt;MemberHub&lt;/a&gt;, I encourage you to do so to connect with more schools and PTA leaders.   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I look forward to meeting many of you at our upcoming event which is tentatively planned for October 16.  In the meantime, please don't hesitate to reach out to me or our Council with any questions you may have.  Thank you again for your service to PTA and your efforts to speak up for every child! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Julie von Haefen&lt;br&gt;
President, Wake County PTA Council&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.wakepta.org/ &quot; onclick=&quot;trackOutboundLink('http://www.wakepta.org/ ')&quot;&gt;www.wakepta.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.facebook.com/wakepta &quot; onclick=&quot;trackOutboundLink('http://www.facebook.com/wakepta ')&quot;&gt;Wake PTA on Facebook&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.twitter.com/wakepta &quot; onclick=&quot;trackOutboundLink('http://www.twitter.com/wakepta ')&quot;&gt;Wake PTA on Twitter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Hello everyone,</summary></entry></feed>