<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.5.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2017-11-28T20:51:01-05:00</updated><id>/</id><title type="html">Brassfield Road Elementary School PTA</title><entry><title type="html">A NEW CLUB AT BRASSFIELD-MORNING MOVEMENT!</title><link href="/events/2018/01/12/club-morning-movement.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A NEW CLUB AT BRASSFIELD-MORNING MOVEMENT!" /><published>2018-01-11T23:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2018-01-11T23:00:00-05:00</updated><id>/events/2018/01/12/club-morning-movement</id><content type="html" xml:base="/events/2018/01/12/club-morning-movement.html">&lt;p&gt;A new club opportunity is coming in January 2018! The Brassfield Morning Movement Club will begin on &lt;strong&gt;Friday, January 5, 2018 for (K-2)&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;amp; &lt;strong&gt;Friday, January 12, 2018 for (3rd-5th.)&lt;/strong&gt; The club will meet from 8:00-8:45 AM on Friday mornings in the Multi-Purpose Room (Gym.) Each age group will meet every other week. The missions of the movement club are to get kids moving and to make them aware of how their breath can help them calm down and focus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;morning-movement-club-faqs&quot;&gt;Morning Movement Club FAQs&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How can I register my child for the club?&lt;/strong&gt; On-line. Look for the web link for the permission/registration on the Brassfield Web Site on Nov. 29th &amp;amp; in the Brassfield Bulletin E-Newsletter during that same week.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What will my child need to bring?&lt;/strong&gt; Each child will need a yoga mat! Your child may bring his or her own mat each week, or he/she may use one that has been donated to the Brassfield PTA for the club.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Will you need parent volunteers?&lt;/strong&gt; Yes! Look for a web link to the Sign Up Genius for Parent Volunteers within the on-line registration form and in upcoming Brassfield Bulletin E-Newsletters. (Note: All volunteers must have Volunteer Clearance with WCPSS)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Who will be leading the club?&lt;/strong&gt;  Parent Volunteers: Amy Buchan (Tr 2) &amp;amp; Jennifer Johnson (Tr 1)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If I have a yoga mat / yoga mats that I’d like to donate to Brassfield PTA to be used by K-5 students, then where should I bring them?&lt;/strong&gt; Beginning Nov. 27th, there will be a large box in the lobby labeled: “Yoga Mat donations for Brassfield Morning Movement Club.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Have additional questions?&lt;/strong&gt; Contact: Amy &amp;amp; Jennifer @ &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:BrassfieldMorningMovementClub@gmail.com&quot;&gt;BrassfieldMorningMovementClub@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">A new club opportunity is coming in January 2018! The Brassfield Morning Movement Club will begin on Friday, January 5, 2018 for (K-2) &amp;amp; Friday, January 12, 2018 for (3rd-5th.) The club will meet from 8:00-8:45 AM on Friday mornings in the Multi-Purpose Room (Gym.) Each age group will meet every other week. The missions of the movement club are to get kids moving and to make them aware of how their breath can help them calm down and focus.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">YEARBOOKS!</title><link href="/events/2018/01/01/yearbooks.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="YEARBOOKS!" /><published>2017-12-31T23:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2017-12-31T23:00:00-05:00</updated><id>/events/2018/01/01/yearbooks</id><content type="html" xml:base="/events/2018/01/01/yearbooks.html">&lt;p&gt;Last week’s yearbook sale notice accidentally omitted a number from the job code - so sorry!  Below is the announcement with the correct code.
YEARBOOKS FOR SALE!
Capture your child’s special school events and memories by purchasing the 2017-18 Brassfield yearbook!  &lt;a href=&quot;https://ybpay.lifetouch.com and enter Job # 9389418&quot;&gt;Online sales are open now&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Basic yearbooks start at $18 with options for hard-cover upgrades and other add-ons. Please contact &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:brassfield.yearbook@gmail.com&quot;&gt;brassfield.yearbook@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt; with any questions.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Last week’s yearbook sale notice accidentally omitted a number from the job code - so sorry! Below is the announcement with the correct code. YEARBOOKS FOR SALE! Capture your child’s special school events and memories by purchasing the 2017-18 Brassfield yearbook! Online sales are open now.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Volunteers Needed</title><link href="/events/2017/12/10/volunteers-needed.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Volunteers Needed" /><published>2017-12-09T23:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2017-12-09T23:00:00-05:00</updated><id>/events/2017/12/10/volunteers-needed</id><content type="html" xml:base="/events/2017/12/10/volunteers-needed.html">&lt;p&gt;The Brassfield PTA needs parent volunteers to assist with maintaining the media center’s math and science kits. Each kit engages children in a different math or science topic through at-home experiments, activities, books, and/or games.  Students may check the kits out weekly during their media center time. The PTA funds all of the kits’ supplies, which are located in the PTA room.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any amount of volunteer help is appreciated, and can be done at any time during school hours. Most kits take just a few minutes each to clean and restock. If you’d like to help out please contact Julie at &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:julschiavone@gmail.com&quot;&gt;julschiavone@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt; or Tara at &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:tarawilk@live.com&quot;&gt;tarawilk@live.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To learn about other opportunities to help at Brassfield for registered volunteers, please visit the following links:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.signupgenius.com/go/5080b4ea9af2eabf58-school&quot;&gt;Assist at a school-wide functions (entire school year dates located here)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.signupgenius.com/go/5080b4ea9af2eabf58-brassfield&quot;&gt;Assist or serve on a PTA committee&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">The Brassfield PTA needs parent volunteers to assist with maintaining the media center’s math and science kits. Each kit engages children in a different math or science topic through at-home experiments, activities, books, and/or games. Students may check the kits out weekly during their media center time. The PTA funds all of the kits’ supplies, which are located in the PTA room.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">BOOK FAIR ACTIVITIES &amp;amp; VOLUNTEERS!</title><link href="/events/2017/12/08/book-fair-activities.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="BOOK FAIR ACTIVITIES &amp; VOLUNTEERS!" /><published>2017-12-07T23:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2017-12-07T23:00:00-05:00</updated><id>/events/2017/12/08/book-fair-activities</id><content type="html" xml:base="/events/2017/12/08/book-fair-activities.html">&lt;p&gt;Holidays are just around the corner. Are the lists generated? A fabulous gift idea for the children in your life is BOOKS!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Brassfield Winter Book Fair is coming soon and will run Nov. 27th - Dec. 8th, open weekdays 8:45am – 4:00pm.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are many opportunities to shop:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Drop off in the morning and pick up in the afternoon&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Come meet your child for lunch and shop the fair together!&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Shop during one of our Book Fair activies– See below!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The book fair needs volunteers throughout the next two weeks. We especially &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.signupgenius.com/go/5080b4ea9af2eabf58-book&quot;&gt;need volunteers&lt;/a&gt; to support your child’s class and others as the kid’s make their book fair selections (help is most needed for the younger kids from 12:45-3:30pm)&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Holidays are just around the corner. Are the lists generated? A fabulous gift idea for the children in your life is BOOKS!</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">PASTRIES FOR PARENTS!</title><link href="/events/2017/12/05/pastries-for-parents.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="PASTRIES FOR PARENTS!" /><published>2017-12-04T23:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2017-12-04T23:00:00-05:00</updated><id>/events/2017/12/05/pastries-for-parents</id><content type="html" xml:base="/events/2017/12/05/pastries-for-parents.html">&lt;p&gt;Pastries for Parents Preorders for Tuesday Morning, 11/28 from 8-8:45am!  Come join your favorite Brassfield Bear for an early morning donut or pastry and support All for Books (books for kids in need) by donating and/or preordering donuts for your office.  Your preorder is especially helpful and you may also order a pizza for next Tuesday’s Media by Moonlight, 12/5: &lt;a href=&quot;https://goo.gl/forms/mG6nUEu3s1Gkjr9w2&quot;&gt;PREORDER HERE&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Pastries for Parents Preorders for Tuesday Morning, 11/28 from 8-8:45am! Come join your favorite Brassfield Bear for an early morning donut or pastry and support All for Books (books for kids in need) by donating and/or preordering donuts for your office. Your preorder is especially helpful and you may also order a pizza for next Tuesday’s Media by Moonlight, 12/5: PREORDER HERE</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">MEDIA BY MOONLIGHT</title><link href="/events/2017/12/05/media-by-moonlight.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="MEDIA BY MOONLIGHT" /><published>2017-12-04T23:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2017-12-04T23:00:00-05:00</updated><id>/events/2017/12/05/media-by-moonlight</id><content type="html" xml:base="/events/2017/12/05/media-by-moonlight.html">&lt;p&gt;Media by Moonlight Tuesday, Dec. 5th, 5:30 – 7:00pm: this will be a great family time with activities, food and books read by staff while parents can peruse all the books available. Pizza will be for sale in the cafeteria OR you can &lt;a href=&quot;https://goo.gl/forms/mG6nUEu3s1Gkjr9w2&quot;&gt;preorder here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Media by Moonlight Tuesday, Dec. 5th, 5:30 – 7:00pm: this will be a great family time with activities, food and books read by staff while parents can peruse all the books available. Pizza will be for sale in the cafeteria OR you can preorder here.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">General PTA meeting, Tuesday Dec. 5th</title><link href="/events/2017/12/05/general-pta-meeting.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="General PTA meeting, Tuesday Dec. 5th" /><published>2017-12-04T23:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2017-12-04T23:00:00-05:00</updated><id>/events/2017/12/05/general-pta-meeting</id><content type="html" xml:base="/events/2017/12/05/general-pta-meeting.html">&lt;p&gt;We hope you can join us on Tuesday, 12/5, for a general PTA Meeting from 4:30-5:30 in the learning commons &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.signupgenius.com/go/5080b4ea9af2eabf58-school&quot;&gt;Childcare available with signup&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">We hope you can join us on Tuesday, 12/5, for a general PTA Meeting from 4:30-5:30 in the learning commons Childcare available with signup.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Cookie Boxes for Teachers and Staff</title><link href="/events/2017/12/01/cookie-boxes.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Cookie Boxes for Teachers and Staff" /><published>2017-11-30T19:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2017-11-30T19:00:00-05:00</updated><id>/events/2017/12/01/cookie-boxes</id><content type="html" xml:base="/events/2017/12/01/cookie-boxes.html">&lt;p&gt;
It's hard to believe the holidays are upon us. That means it's almost time to get out the flour and sugar and send some good cheer to all of the teachers and staff at Brassfield who do so much for our children every day. Each year, the PTA Staff Appreciation &amp; Hospitality Committee, together with the support of our wonderful parent volunteers, assembles a box of homemade cookies for each teacher and staff member at the school. We hear countless compliments and words of thanks for doing this and have been told repeatedly it's one of the favorite days of the school year. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;indent&quot; style=&quot;color: red&quot;&gt;
UPDATE! We are currently short 125 dozen cookies.  The staff loves the cookie boxes provided by Brassfield families at the holidays.  No time to bake?  Store bought are perfect for all, but especially for our staff with GF and Dairy Free allergies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To sign up please go to &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.signupgenius.com/go/10C0B4DAEA628A64-holiday1&quot;&gt;Holiday Cookie Boxes&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/holiday_cookie_boxes.jpg&quot; width=&quot;335&quot; height=&quot;225&quot; alt=&quot;holiday_cookie_boxes.jpg&quot;&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">It's hard to believe the holidays are upon us. That means it's almost time to get out the flour and sugar and send some good cheer to all of the teachers and staff at Brassfield who do so much for our children every day. Each year, the PTA Staff Appreciation &amp; Hospitality Committee, together with the support of our wonderful parent volunteers, assembles a box of homemade cookies for each teacher and staff member at the school. We hear countless compliments and words of thanks for doing this and have been told repeatedly it's one of the favorite days of the school year. UPDATE! We are currently short 125 dozen cookies. The staff loves the cookie boxes provided by Brassfield families at the holidays. No time to bake? Store bought are perfect for all, but especially for our staff with GF and Dairy Free allergies. To sign up please go to Holiday Cookie Boxes.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">BOOK FAIR IS COMING!</title><link href="/past_events/2017/11/27/book-fair.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="BOOK FAIR IS COMING!" /><published>2017-11-26T23:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2017-11-26T23:00:00-05:00</updated><id>/past_events/2017/11/27/book-fair</id><content type="html" xml:base="/past_events/2017/11/27/book-fair.html">&lt;p&gt;Book Fair is coming 11/27-12/8! More information coming soon!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Book Fair is coming 11/27-12/8! More information coming soon!</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">FUNDRAISER for BOOKS! – Who will win??!</title><link href="/past_events/2017/11/13/fundraiser-for-books.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="FUNDRAISER for BOOKS! -- Who will win??!" /><published>2017-11-12T23:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2017-11-12T23:00:00-05:00</updated><id>/past_events/2017/11/13/fundraiser-for-books</id><content type="html" xml:base="/past_events/2017/11/13/fundraiser-for-books.html">&lt;p&gt;Next week, 11/13-11/17, we will be doing a change drive to help raise money for
kids in local communities who need books!  Any additional money raised may be
used to buy books for our school library or help teachers refresh their
classroom libraries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bring in those pennies, nickels, dimes and quarters to fill the jug in the
lobby. Who will be able to fill the jug faster, boys or girls? As an added
bonus, Scholastic will purchase a book for each $1 raised and provide up to
1 million books to charities such as the Kids In Need Foundation, Reader to
Reader, Inc., and the National Center for Families Learning.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Next week, 11/13-11/17, we will be doing a change drive to help raise money for kids in local communities who need books! Any additional money raised may be used to buy books for our school library or help teachers refresh their classroom libraries.</summary></entry></feed>