<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.5.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2017-11-14T19:24:09-05:00</updated><id>/</id><title type="html">Brassfield Road Elementary School PTA</title><entry><title type="html">Volunteers Needed</title><link href="/events/2017/12/10/volunteers-needed.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Volunteers Needed" /><published>2017-12-09T23:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2017-12-09T23:00:00-05:00</updated><id>/events/2017/12/10/volunteers-needed</id><content type="html" xml:base="/events/2017/12/10/volunteers-needed.html">&lt;p&gt;The Brassfield PTA needs parent volunteers to assist with maintaining the media center’s math and science kits. Each kit engages children in a different math or science topic through at-home experiments, activities, books, and/or games.  Students may check the kits out weekly during their media center time. The PTA funds all of the kits’ supplies, which are located in the PTA room.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any amount of volunteer help is appreciated, and can be done at any time during school hours. Most kits take just a few minutes each to clean and restock. If you’d like to help out please contact Julie at &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:julschiavone@gmail.com&quot;&gt;julschiavone@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt; or Tara at &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:tarawilk@live.com&quot;&gt;tarawilk@live.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To learn about other opportunities to help at Brassfield for registered volunteers, please visit the following links:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.signupgenius.com/go/5080b4ea9af2eabf58-school&quot;&gt;Assist at a school-wide functions (entire school year dates located here)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.signupgenius.com/go/5080b4ea9af2eabf58-brassfield&quot;&gt;Assist or serve on a PTA committee&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">The Brassfield PTA needs parent volunteers to assist with maintaining the media center’s math and science kits. Each kit engages children in a different math or science topic through at-home experiments, activities, books, and/or games. Students may check the kits out weekly during their media center time. The PTA funds all of the kits’ supplies, which are located in the PTA room.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Cookie Boxes for Teachers and Staff</title><link href="/events/2017/12/01/cookie-boxes.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Cookie Boxes for Teachers and Staff" /><published>2017-11-30T19:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2017-11-30T19:00:00-05:00</updated><id>/events/2017/12/01/cookie-boxes</id><content type="html" xml:base="/events/2017/12/01/cookie-boxes.html">&lt;p&gt;
It's hard to believe the holidays are upon us. That means it's almost time to get out the flour and sugar and send some good cheer to all of the teachers and staff at Brassfield who do so much for our children every day. Each year, the PTA Staff Appreciation &amp; Hospitality Committee, together with the support of our wonderful parent volunteers, assembles a box of homemade cookies for each teacher and staff member at the school. We hear countless compliments and words of thanks for doing this and have been told repeatedly it's one of the favorite days of the school year. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To sign up please go to &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.signupgenius.com/go/10C0B4DAEA628A64-holiday1&quot;&gt;Holiday Cookie Boxes&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/holiday_cookie_boxes.jpg&quot; width=&quot;335&quot; height=&quot;225&quot; alt=&quot;holiday_cookie_boxes.jpg&quot;&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">It's hard to believe the holidays are upon us. That means it's almost time to get out the flour and sugar and send some good cheer to all of the teachers and staff at Brassfield who do so much for our children every day. Each year, the PTA Staff Appreciation &amp; Hospitality Committee, together with the support of our wonderful parent volunteers, assembles a box of homemade cookies for each teacher and staff member at the school. We hear countless compliments and words of thanks for doing this and have been told repeatedly it's one of the favorite days of the school year. To sign up please go to Holiday Cookie Boxes.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">BOOK FAIR IS COMING!</title><link href="/events/2017/11/27/book-fair.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="BOOK FAIR IS COMING!" /><published>2017-11-26T23:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2017-11-26T23:00:00-05:00</updated><id>/events/2017/11/27/book-fair</id><content type="html" xml:base="/events/2017/11/27/book-fair.html">&lt;p&gt;Book Fair is coming 11/27-12/8! More information coming soon!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Book Fair is coming 11/27-12/8! More information coming soon!</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">FUNDRAISER for BOOKS! – Who will win??!</title><link href="/events/2017/11/13/fundraiser-for-books.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="FUNDRAISER for BOOKS! -- Who will win??!" /><published>2017-11-12T23:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2017-11-12T23:00:00-05:00</updated><id>/events/2017/11/13/fundraiser-for-books</id><content type="html" xml:base="/events/2017/11/13/fundraiser-for-books.html">&lt;p&gt;Next week, 11/13-11/17, we will be doing a change drive to help raise money for
kids in local communities who need books!  Any additional money raised may be
used to buy books for our school library or help teachers refresh their
classroom libraries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bring in those pennies, nickels, dimes and quarters to fill the jug in the
lobby. Who will be able to fill the jug faster, boys or girls? As an added
bonus, Scholastic will purchase a book for each $1 raised and provide up to
1 million books to charities such as the Kids In Need Foundation, Reader to
Reader, Inc., and the National Center for Families Learning.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Next week, 11/13-11/17, we will be doing a change drive to help raise money for kids in local communities who need books! Any additional money raised may be used to buy books for our school library or help teachers refresh their classroom libraries.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Brassfield Holiday Bears are now Available</title><link href="/events/2017/11/12/holiday-bears.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Brassfield Holiday Bears are now Available" /><published>2017-11-11T19:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2017-11-11T19:00:00-05:00</updated><id>/events/2017/11/12/holiday-bears</id><content type="html" xml:base="/events/2017/11/12/holiday-bears.html">&lt;img class=&quot;pull-right&quot; src=&quot;/assets/beartree.jpg&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;color: blue; font-size: larger&quot;&gt;Tracks 2,3,4 Help Needed!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;color: green&quot;&gt;Support a fellow Brassfield family&lt;/span&gt; by picking out &quot;&lt;span style=&quot;color: green&quot;&gt;Bear Tree&lt;/span&gt;&quot; bears to help ensure that &lt;i&gt;all&lt;/i&gt; Brassfield students have a happy holiday season.  Please stop by our front office to pick out a bear with gift ideas for a child from Ms. Edgreen.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Tracks 2,3,4 Help Needed! Support a fellow Brassfield family by picking out &quot;Bear Tree&quot; bears to help ensure that all Brassfield students have a happy holiday season. Please stop by our front office to pick out a bear with gift ideas for a child from Ms. Edgreen.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Spirit Night - 11/8, Wednesday, Moe’s - Wakefield</title><link href="/past_events/2017/11/08/moe.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Spirit Night - 11/8, Wednesday, Moe's - Wakefield" /><published>2017-11-07T23:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2017-11-07T23:00:00-05:00</updated><id>/past_events/2017/11/08/moe</id><content type="html" xml:base="/past_events/2017/11/08/moe.html">&lt;p&gt;
Get ready for Brassfield night at Moe’s and Rainbow Day!
Show your school spirit and wear the color for your grade then join in the fun at Moe’s!
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Kindergarten- Yellow&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;1st- Orange&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;2nd - Red&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;3rd - Blue&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;4th - Green&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;5th - Purple&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;https://gm1.ggpht.com/w9RZ_j44iFwXv4AZveUOGBfkTItd3SXowk3u5eh1dwKYM9RPCqVX-GgCZOFDMcOvOLwgNx7uuxzxP8gaJ6j9chGBpB6rm18pVwpAYZLy4GBFrckA2esgytnrVJTvic5sn2I1AsGj48Pdi2bwhNFa6XusG6J19ROUOcRXQxLuIkB_bSuv5wuJ-DXjpJwUA8-fRrU7BoYhU2d1lOJTBgp8AbJtd0XxIIpHkBeAuuFIo3dlDl2ZyfC0Y-PGvt00ccqJqFWBAvw5etjsLeh3N0PYzn6uGG_7jhMy1H0b4e63lczXFww3ZLJpVJ_ZH4YG_6mzCpFpvVAdaB7TvJA82WS6ojr3uTUwpQC9e512a1-5hdR9f6kUwoiJvpQv5S-X2YFzdNzKAmA9yg5hTAhL4WR9js89TBSSWZlu8SQ6byjpjShun2oGrkQw2-aNe5sbhfr1sFPPLGz8N1CirSWc7qPTEoLMNSUdBRdwxV9634KKLFxkNoHujP_ZmRzG3Pw4ldHFrVQZVOa09grH2bXzhSZQFoHXjAU56qMJdJVYh2UL56set7DNzus6zGdHt5rR_uvXfb-3P5TtyChKl0wbuJCoPA0oDO_wF7LIt49SWz2OlxBzrko-oJ9sFXI2ZMGDwr4Vyzn8yAH--WLKBEJLPm6lf5tR7CTxjEuvMom_7yLIO_4Nwuw-51THpxtI4NvllQ=w724-h944-l75-ft&quot;&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Get ready for Brassfield night at Moe’s and Rainbow Day! Show your school spirit and wear the color for your grade then join in the fun at Moe’s! Kindergarten- Yellow 1st- Orange 2nd - Red 3rd - Blue 4th - Green 5th - Purple</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Character Parade - Tuesday, 10/31</title><link href="/past_events/2017/10/31/character-parade.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Character Parade - Tuesday, 10/31" /><published>2017-10-31T13:45:00-04:00</published><updated>2017-10-31T13:45:00-04:00</updated><id>/past_events/2017/10/31/character-parade</id><content type="html" xml:base="/past_events/2017/10/31/character-parade.html">&lt;p&gt;Calling all characters! Book characters, that is! In a celebration of reading, Brassfield students will parade the school on October 31st carrying their favorite book, dressed as their favorite character. Classrooms across the school will tie the experience to grade level curriculum. From Winnie the Pooh to Harry Potter we can't wait to bring books to life! Be on the lookout for specific information on how to participate from your teacher. Track 3 families are encouraged to come back to school and participate, but be sure to check into the front office with Kimberly when you arrive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;signed&quot;&gt;Registered Volunteers - &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.signupgenius.com/go/5080b4ea9af2eabf58-school&quot;&gt;Sign up to assist&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Calling all characters! Book characters, that is! In a celebration of reading, Brassfield students will parade the school on October 31st carrying their favorite book, dressed as their favorite character. Classrooms across the school will tie the experience to grade level curriculum. From Winnie the Pooh to Harry Potter we can't wait to bring books to life! Be on the lookout for specific information on how to participate from your teacher. Track 3 families are encouraged to come back to school and participate, but be sure to check into the front office with Kimberly when you arrive. Registered Volunteers - Sign up to assist</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Artopia after Early Release! Friday, 10/20</title><link href="/past_events/2017/10/20/artopia.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Artopia after Early Release! Friday, 10/20" /><published>2017-10-20T13:45:00-04:00</published><updated>2017-10-20T13:45:00-04:00</updated><id>/past_events/2017/10/20/artopia</id><content type="html" xml:base="/past_events/2017/10/20/artopia.html">&lt;p&gt;Join us at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.artopia-raleigh.com/book-online&quot;&gt;ARTOPIA&lt;/a&gt; on Oct. 20th for early release! We will have 2 sessions available one from 1:45 - 2:45 and the second from 3:00 - 4:00, as well as the  option to add on an Artarama hour.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions please contact &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:katiescott22@gmail.com&quot;&gt;Katie Scott&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The $12 session will include a variety of fall crafts! The artarama hour is a 1hour canvas painting session and is open to children 3+ and adults.  Please use the link below to register online, scroll down until you see the Brassfield Fundraiser, you can add on the Artarama hour at checkout!  Don’t forget 50% comes back to Brassfield!</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Join us at ARTOPIA on Oct. 20th for early release! We will have 2 sessions available one from 1:45 - 2:45 and the second from 3:00 - 4:00, as well as the option to add on an Artarama hour. If you have any questions please contact Katie Scott</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">K-3 Mandate Presentation and Discussion - PLEASE REGISTER</title><link href="/past_events/2017/10/16/k-3-mandate-presentation.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="K-3 Mandate Presentation and Discussion - PLEASE REGISTER" /><published>2017-10-16T19:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2017-10-16T19:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/past_events/2017/10/16/k-3-mandate-presentation</id><content type="html" xml:base="/past_events/2017/10/16/k-3-mandate-presentation.html">&lt;p&gt;
What: Advocacy Presentation and Discussion&lt;br&gt;
Who will be presenting: Wake County PTA Council and Public Schools First NC&lt;br&gt;
When:&lt;b&gt;Monday, 10/16&lt;/b&gt;, from 7-8pm&lt;br&gt;
Where: Brassfield Road Elementary School Media Center&lt;br&gt;
For:  Brassfield, Baileywick, and Wakefield ES parents and area PTA Boards.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;signed&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.SignUpGenius.com/go/5080B4EA9AF2EABF58-advocacy&quot;&gt;Please RSVP to attend here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The North Carolina Legislature passed an unfunded K-3 class size mandate
last spring which will take full effect in 2018-2019.  Join us on October
16 to hear about the mandate, how it will affect Wake County Public
Schools, and the possible solutions offered by the school district to deal
with the new requirements.  We will also discuss what PTA units, leaders,
members and parents can do to advocate for our students and teachers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Come join us to be part of an open discussion of strategy ideas to affect
change! Questions? &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:school@gopack.org&quot;&gt;Tania&lt;/a&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">What: Advocacy Presentation and Discussion Who will be presenting: Wake County PTA Council and Public Schools First NC When:Monday, 10/16, from 7-8pm Where: Brassfield Road Elementary School Media Center For: Brassfield, Baileywick, and Wakefield ES parents and area PTA Boards. Please RSVP to attend here.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Book Fair Volunteer Information Session - Monday, 10/16</title><link href="/past_events/2017/10/16/book-fair.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Book Fair Volunteer Information Session - Monday, 10/16" /><published>2017-10-16T14:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2017-10-16T14:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/past_events/2017/10/16/book-fair</id><content type="html" xml:base="/past_events/2017/10/16/book-fair.html">&lt;p&gt;The book fair committee is looking for volunteers to help with our Winter Book Fair!  We will have an informational meeting at 2:00pm on Monday, October 16th in the Learning Commons to go over areas where help is needed and the estimated time commitment for each job.  Some items can even be done from home, and no amount of help is too small! This year, all proceeds from the fair will go towards improving our library collection, so please stop in and see how you can help make this fundraiser a success! Questions? &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:Ericatadd@Hotmail.com&quot;&gt;Email Erica Tadd&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;signed&quot;&gt;-Thanks,The Book Fair Committee&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">The book fair committee is looking for volunteers to help with our Winter Book Fair! We will have an informational meeting at 2:00pm on Monday, October 16th in the Learning Commons to go over areas where help is needed and the estimated time commitment for each job. Some items can even be done from home, and no amount of help is too small! This year, all proceeds from the fair will go towards improving our library collection, so please stop in and see how you can help make this fundraiser a success! Questions? Email Erica Tadd -Thanks,The Book Fair Committee</summary></entry></feed>